{
    "A": [
    {
      "question":"nearest star to earth",
     "answer":"sun",
     "id":1
    },
    {
      "question":"1+1",
     "answer":"2",
     "id":2
   },
   { 
    "question":"1+2",
    "answer":"3",
    "id":3
   },
   {
     "question":"1+3",
     "answer":"4",
     "id":4
   },
   {
     "question":"1+4",
     "answer":"5",
     "id":5
   },
   {
     "question":"1+5",
     "answer":"6",
     "id":6
   },
   {
     "question":"1+6",
     "answer":"7",
     "id":7
   },
   {
     "question":"1+7",
     "answer":"8",
     "id":8
   },
   {
     "question":"1+8",
     "answer":"9",
     "id":9
   },
   {
     "question":"1+9",
     "answer":"10",
     "id":10
   }
   ]
}